

Kyle Orciuch

Aspiring Software

Engineer & Data Scientist

Contact

korciuch@stanford.edu (219) 616-0425 https://k.orciuch.org https://github.com/korciuch

Skills

Coding Languages

C, C#, C++, Python, Javascript, SQL

Framework Systems:

ASP.NET Core, React.js, Django Rest, Keras, TensorFlow

References

Director of Men's

Soccer

Stanford University Athletic Department

Jeremy Gunn jgunn@stanford.edu

Awards

PAC-12 Champion ('18) AP Scholar with Distinction

Career Summary

Backend Developer

The Carta Project

JAN 2021 TO PRESENT

Focused on checking backend API endpoints' behavior when mocking client requests.

Worked in tandem with the frontend team & product managers to implement new functionality to the beta website (http://cartabeta.stanford.edu).

Web Development & Consulting Intern

NGS, Ltd.

JUN 2020 TO SEP 2020

Attended client and project meetings to identify and document user requirements. Engineered websites using web development frameworks such as ASP.NET Core. Tracked changes to source code via Bitbucket.

Sports Science Intern Stanford University Athletic Department

JUL 2018 TO JUL 2019

Compiled and documented statistical information for athlete load reports derived from GPS tracker units. Extracted and exported athlete performance data into various database applications for review.

Educational Training

BS Candidate, Computer Science Stanford University

SEP 2018 TO JUN 2022 (EXPECTED) **GPA**: 3.3

Major Track: Artificial Intelligence Activities: Varsity Men's Soccer

Key Courses:

CS 109 (Probability for Computer Scientists), CS 110 (Principles of Computing Systems), CS 161 (Design & Analysis of Algorithms), CS 230 (Deep Learning)

Portfolio

(REPOS AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST)

Diagnosing Thoracic Abnormalities with Deep Learning

CS 230 - MAR 2021

Personal Portfolio Website (React.js, Chakra UI)

DEC 2020

Custom Threadpool & Multithreaded RSS Aggregator (C++)

CS 110 - MAY 2020

Implicit & Explicit Heap Allocators (C)

CS 107 - MAR 2020